http://www.marineterms.com/more/privacy-policy.html

Home
Directory
Manufacturers Brands Ship Equipment Repairs Ship Equipment Suppliers Ship Repairs Contractors Safety Equipment Ship Services Suppliers
Surveys - Inspections Directories & Guides Education, Training Law, Insurance, Finance Online Market Organisations, Associations
Surveyors & Consultants
Divers Worldwide
Shipbuilders Shipyards
Software Solutions Ship Owners & Shipping Other Categories Yachts & Boats
Sofware
IDENTIFICATION.   Holder: IOANNIDIS GEORGE TITLE: INFOMARINE ON-LINE - BESTDOMAINS TAX ID No.: 027544666 Registered office: 33 Akti Miaouli str. Piraeus 18756 - Greece Registry data: www.infomarine.gr www.infomarine.net www.shipyards.gr www.bestdomains.gr Email: support@infomarine.gr Data Protection Officer (DPO): The User may contact the DPO through the following email address: support@infomarine.gr, or by writing to the address of INFOMARINE ON-LINE marked for the attention of the “Data Protection Officer”.
This privacy policy sets out how Infomarine On-Line  uses and protects any information that you give  when you use this website.
Infomarine On-Line is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
This privacy policy sets out how Infomarine On-Line  uses and protects any information that you give  when you use this website.
Infomarine On-Line is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Infomarine On-Line may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st May 2018 in order to comply with the new General Regulations on Data Protection (EU Regulation 2016/679) that will come into effect on 25 May 2018, we have updated our Privacy Policy, which you can read here.
What we collect
We may collect the following information: Identification data: Company Name Contact details: Website, Postal address, mobile telephone number, email address. Data corresponding to the Infomarine On-Line Maritime Directory programme. User ID codes or passwords Details of preferences. Geolocation data. Personal data as name, surname(s), required for payment of the services offered trough the websites same as well as to pay for the services associated with it.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping. We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. We may send our Newsletters to your registered email and you may Unsubscribe at any time. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties.
What we publish in our Directories
Identification data: Company Name Contact details: Website, Postal address, mobile telephone number,  any related information of your services and products found intersting for promotion to the vistors in directories.  .
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by us for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind to unsubscribe from our data at any time by writing to or emailing us at support@infomarine.gr  This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it.
We will never sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties in our own newsletters which we think you may find interesting, if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about free of charge under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Infomarine On-Line, 33 Akti Miaouli str,Piraeus 18535, Greece.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us or contact https://www.infomarine.gr/more/contact.html as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Date of last update: 22 May 2018
IDENTIFICATION.   Holder: IOANNIDIS GEORGE TITLE: INFOMARINE ON-LINE - BESTDOMAINS TAX ID No.: 027544666 Registered office: 33 Akti Miaouli str. Piraeus 18756 - Greece Registry data: www.infomarine.gr www.infomarine.net www.shipyards.gr www.bestdomains.gr Email: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. Data Protection Officer (DPO): The User may contact the DPO through the following email address: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it., or by writing to the address of INFOMARINE ON-LINE marked for the attention of the “Data Protection Officer”.
This privacy policy sets out how Infomarine On-Line  uses and protects any information that you give  when you use this website.
Infomarine On-Line is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
This privacy policy sets out how Infomarine On-Line  uses and protects any information that you give  when you use this website.
Infomarine On-Line is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
Infomarine On-Line may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st May 2018 in order to comply with the new General Regulations on Data Protection (EU Regulation 2016/679) that will come into effect on 25 May 2018, we have updated our Privacy Policy, which you can read here.
What we collect
We may collect the following information: Identification data: Company Name Contact details: Website, Postal address, mobile telephone number, email address. Data corresponding to the Infomarine On-Line Maritime Directory programme. User ID codes or passwords Details of preferences. Geolocation data. Personal data as name, surname(s), required for payment of the services offered trough the websites same as well as to pay for the services associated with it.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping. We may use the information to improve our products and services. We may periodically send promotional email about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests. We may send our Newsletters to your registered email and you may Unsubscribe at any time. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties.
What we publish in our Directories
Identification data: Company Name Contact details: Website, Postal address, mobile telephone number,  any related information of your services and products found intersting for promotion to the vistors in directories.  .
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by us for direct marketing purposes if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind to unsubscribe from our data at any time by writing to or emailing us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.  This e-mail address is being protected from spam bots, you need JavaScript enabled to view it.
We will never sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties in our own newsletters which we think you may find interesting, if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about free of charge under the Data Protection Act 1998. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Infomarine On-Line, 33 Akti Miaouli str,Piraeus 18535, Greece.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us or contact https://www.infomarine.gr/more/contact.html as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Date of last update: 22 May 2018
Companies Profiles
SKF HELLAS SA
SKF has been a leading global technology provider since 1907. Our fundamental stre...
Read more
Companies Profiles
Turbo Spirit - Turbo Theomar
TURBO SPIRIT in partnership with TURBO THEOMAR are specialised Turbocharger's Spare parts suppliers ...
Read more
Companies Profiles
C. SAVVAS Ltd - General Ship Repairs and...
C. SAVVAS Ltd was established in 2002 by Mr. Costas E. Savva who has been active in the field of mar...
Read more
Companies Profiles
IPPOKRATIS KOYTSIANAS & Co.
The Company IPPOCRATIS KOUTSIANAS & CO, has been active in the Shipping and Industrial field for...
Read more
Companies Profiles
Seametrix - Sea Distance & Voyage Estimation
Seametrix is an advanced and detailed sea distance calculation and voyage estimati...
Read more
Companies Profiles
Daka Sealing Systems
Our company established in 1984, operates and specializes in the field of sealing ...
Read more
Companies Profiles
MONDIAL TECHNICS
"MONDIAL TECHNICS" ESTABLISHED 1990, BASED AT PIRAEUS AND ACTING AS AGENT OF COMPANY'S WHICH C...
Read more
Companies Profiles
TRANSMARE SHIPPING & TRADING CO. LTD.
Our company which has 30 years experience with Professional Experts in marine sector. We are the aut...
Read more
Companies Profiles
Aspida Maritime Security Corp
Aspida is an experienced private maritime security company (PMSC) offering a comprehensive range of ...
Read more
Companies Profiles
Daihan Anchor Chain Mfg. Co Ltd
DaiHan Anchor Chain Mfg. Co., Ltd. is a global market leader in anchor chains and accessories....
Read more
Companies Profiles
PSOMAKARA Diving Services & Consulting Co
PSOMAKARA Diving Services & Consulting Co was founded in 1992 in Greece; conso...
Read more
Companies Profiles
PRI GREEN FUEL PROGRAM
We at Power Research Inc. know that you are interested in conserving and protecting your personal as...
Read more
This website uses cookies to manage authentication, navigation, and other functions.
By using our website, you agree that we can place these types of cookies on your device.
View Privacy Policy
I decline
I agree
